pioneer-tw.com 2016-01-05

# Aquaculture Equipment, Paddlewheel Aerator Manufacturer - Pioneer A.E. Company Limited

##  [ Home ](http://www.pioneer-tw.com/index.asp?lang=2) > [ About Us ](http://www.pioneer-tw.com/style/frame/templates22/about.asp?lang=2&customer_id=1837&name_id=68818&content_set=color_1)

## About Us

### Introduction

**Pioneer Group **has been established in the southern part of Taiwan since 1999 with it’s headquarter located in Kaohsiung, the most beautiful harbor city, and factory in Sinying, Tainan County. Our team consists of Reputed Aquaculture Specialist, Professional Mechanical Engineer and Experienced Installing Technicians to fulfill the different Aquaculture requirements and develop the most ideal, innovative and cost effective equipments with its 100% attention on the quality, durability, performance and customers’ profitability.

Due to our insisting in strict quality control and upgrading our equipment continuously, which allow **Pioneer Group** being the well-known number one brand in the America Continent as well as expending its high market rates to the rest 4 continents rapidly, thus, more and more ** Pioneer Group **products can be seen in those important Aquaculture territories worldwide.

**_Business Scope_**

  1. Aquaculture Equipment : Paddlewheel Aerators ("Teco" Motor made in "Taiwan" under ISO9001/ISO14001), Air-Injectors, Automatic Feeders, Roots/Rings Blowers (ISO9001), and Water Pumps (ISO9002).   

  2. Cage Farming System & Accessories. (Turnkey Package Offered !)   

  3. Automatic Grits Manufacturing Machines, Mixer Machines, Fish Chopping Machines, Fish Mincing Machines.   

  4. Power Control Panels (ISO9001).   

  5. Electrical Cables (ISO9001).   

  6. HDPE Pond Liner (ISO9002).   

  7. Aquaculture Consultant Service… etc.   

**THE COMPANY'S PHILOSOPHY IS TO PROVIDE TOP QUALITY PRODUCTS AND GENUINE **" PROFESSIONAL" **SERVICES TO THE CUSTOMER & FULLY SATISFY THEIR NEEDS IN THE MOST ECONOMICAL WAY!**

As the American Continent’s most distinguished Taiwan-Made Paddlewheel Aerator brand, **Pioneer Group **equipments have been selling globally for many years and obtaining the sound reputations and satisfactions from the clients, furthermore, several hundreds of its Cage Farming Systems have been widely used not only by the largest tilapia farm in the world but also some governmental projects in the Asian Continent due to its insisting on the **"Professionalism, Top Quality, Unique Design & Attractive Price"**.

To get more details or exchange some ideas on how to increase the Paddlewheel Aerator and Cage Farming System's **"Performances/Costs Savings"** , please do contact us freely.

We guarantee your total satisfactions with our product's quality and back up services ! 

### Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY (Updated on 14nd August, 2011)**

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the www.pioneer-tw.com which is operated by Pioneer Group. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and www.pioneer-tw.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept. Other websites which are linked to/from www.pioneer-tw.com may have different policies. If you have any question about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to Contact us. 

**The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Pioneer Group may collect the following types of information:  
**Registration Information:** At the time you register to become a Member of the Site, you will be asked to complete an application form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information.") 

We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which Pioneer Group determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, news, activities information, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. Please note if you choose not to provide it, you may not be able to enjoy the right and benefit as a registered user. 

You can instruct us whether or not you wish to be contacted by checking or removing the check from the box indicating your preference as applicable at the place where your information is collected, or by other means (such as an e-mail request). In addition, with each communication you receive from Pioneer Group, you will be given the opportunity to indicate if you do not wish to receive future communications. 

**Payment Information:** Your payment information may be collected when any online shop or order occurred on www.pioneer-tw.com. We may use your payment information to materialize the deal. Every purchase and order is governed by the Sales Policy which set out your rights and obligations with respect to your purchases, including important limitations and exclusions. Your placement of an order or purchase at Pioneer Group constitutes your agreement that these policies apply to the order, so please be certain you understand and accept them before you submit any order.

**Log Information:** For each visitor to the Site, the Site automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor's IP address/domain name combination and any referring websites. We use this information to understand visitor traffic patterns through our websites for purposes such as enhancing their usability. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you've activated blocking technology available in some browsers.

**Cookies:** When you visit the Site, we send one or more cookies which store certain information on your computer to your computer or other device. We use cookies to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies, we may not able to restore any preferences or customization setting you previously specified, and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions. 

**Third Party Applications** –Pioneer Group may make available third party applications, such as eTradeAsia, through its services. The information collected by Pioneer Group when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies.

**Disclosure of Information**

Pioneer Group reserves the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Pioneer Group, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

Pioneer Group also reserves the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of Terms of Use Agreement or any agreement with Pioneer Group, we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Pioneer Group or others.

**Minors**

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

**Security Measures**

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Member, your Registration Information can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., Member ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Pioneer Group in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that www.pioneer-tw.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information www. 網址.com 's possession. This Privacy Policy was last amended on August 14, 2011
